Ha, crazy guy.
It can't be beautiful.
Maybe you like it
Did you fold it?
No...
When I think about it
I haven't even tried it
just
I'm in a bit of trouble right now
Maybe there's a reason you're having trouble...
- No way
- No way, what?
Correct answer
My younger sister, who is a senior in high school, is actually Seonwoohae's daughter.
Ding
Oh, what are you doing?
Correct answer!
Then Kim Seok-ju is his biological brother.
Oh, wait a minute, then
Is this the CEO’s son?
- that's right?
- Ding
-What am I doing now?
- Jeong, correct answer!
Then, huh?
Is your hair a wig?
How long has it been going on?
What are you saying?
This is really my hair
Can I pull it?
ah!
This is real
Why do you think so quickly?
Well, first place in the whole school
It must have been in vain, I
Ha...
Ah! Wow, really
I don't think I'm crazy
me now?
It's okay, I'm not crazy right now
So when do we become sane?
well
Yeah, you don't know
Once I decided
I want to break through
I have chosen
I have to see it through to the end.
Breakthrough?
You said you would?
look forward to it
Ouch!
I have to, is it lunch yet?
While I was developing this new menu,
Lunchbox perfect...
What are you doing?
What did the doctor say?
Well, it hasn't gotten any worse, right?
brother
Couldn't the result be wrong?
I don't think it feels real yet.
Hey
Let’s eat rice first, this won’t taste good if it gets cold.
Let's eat
Mix it a little from the bottom.
Oh, you mix it?
Seonwoo has to do this?
Why aren't you showing any sign, senior?
Oh, really!
Just do it!
Oh, sorry
You and I
I guess I found the same person
- Yes?
- Do you know Jin Moo-young?
Ah, that damn Jin Moo-young
You managed to appear on the show, this guy.
How did you convince me?
You've had some trouble, casting, last year.
It's cooler than it looks, there's a lot to it.
Local filming was a mess.
I stayed alone and planted all the trees
That should be clearly visible, right?
'Cause that's what we do
I think you must have been very unhappy that day.
I sincerely apologize
I felt like this
I have no intention of receiving it
I feel like I'm being forced to receive it
The apology was sincere.
I don't want to take it, I don't have to take it
For that human
You know what a wasteful person you are, right?
the name
Isn't it your mother's name?
I even wrote a pen name
behind the name
Didn't you want to hide?
It's obvious that you'll get criticized
A person involved in a fraud case
Publish a book to show off
If you make a living selling copyright
There will be more when it airs today.
Are you worried?
Even if it's hard, hold on tight
For no reason I don’t care about the people around me
Thanks for the advice
Enjoy your meal
Why do I have so much energy?
Did you fight with the lady?
Just like a punching bag
It should be right
The moment the man
I can't control my temper
Do you know how to lose your temper?
When I lived with my mom, I was Seok-ju’s oppa.
I don’t think I saw it when I was living there.
I can’t stand it in front of kids, me too.
you
Do you remember when you were young?
Mom ran away
Hold your hand uncle
The first time I went to see my brother
Nuri
Don’t you miss mom?
You didn’t ask me even once?
I don't know
If I do that then something
I feel like I'm betraying my brother.
If you need a place to confide in
You know there’s an uncle, right?
ruler!
Can I order kimchi fried rice too?
Yeah
Here's kimchi... Ah!
Hey, you gave me kimchi.
You can't talk about it, okay?
Meeting you man
You have to keep it a secret
When are you going to reconcile?
It's been 10 years since you've been doing this through me.
This is
the sun forgives
It's a problem that needs to be addressed...
Hey, this is it, huh?
When I was young
Uncle with this
I took a lot of pictures
Oh my, you're pretty
Oh, that's right
When are you going to give me the film?
Oh no
This is thirty-six shots...
How can you not contact me at least once?
Aunt
hello
Hey, take this and go quickly.
My uncle will call me.
you do it
Now even minors...
Were you here for this?
Sister!
Oh, really!
In front of a girl who was like my daughter...
Yes, I met a girl who was like my daughter.
Let's start with the police station.
Come here, come here!
Students come along too!
It's me, it's Nuri
Don't you remember me?
They gave me this camera a long time ago.
Ah...
yes
You are enjoying it
The little boy that Seok-ju brought in.
- Seonwoohae's daughter
- Yes?
Not my daughter
The daughter of a woman I met before...
- Huh...
- I told you, that
Before going to my sister
When my mom dies and I have a hard time
The woman I loved...
Hey! you!
You can't even lie
Why are you hiding so much, huh?
Ah, when we talk about old times
You don't like it
And I do this
I didn't know I'd get caught
Just keep your mouth open, really
I'm no one's daughter
Uncle, Aunty, don't fight
hello there
Uh, hi
I'll explain everything
Our sun shines brightly
I'm living a good life
Kid...
Yes, yes, I am a sinner, I am
- Ah! I can't see
- Surprise, surprise.
- Oh, I'm going crazy, ah...
- Oh, what a surprise.
Hey! Hey, hey, hey, hey
Like this, like this
Drink it up
- Huh?
- wait for a sec
Hey, hey, hey
Do not eat on an empty stomach
Ha...
I guess I should have drank soju beforehand
See you next week after drinking in advance.
ok
Ah, but I really can't see it.
- Do it?
- Uh
Do it quickly!
evil! Ah, why is he like that?
Ah, why are you acting so cute?
Oh my
- Brother, calculate here.
- Uh, counting.
Thank you, come again
thank you
- Hey, snack number 7 came out.
- Uh, I'll do it.
Oh, that's right
Isn’t today soccer day?
- yes?
- That's right.
- Me, boss.
- Yes
Please play soccer
Oh, yes, soccer?
Wait a minute
Still, today went well
Just me
Is it fun?
me too
It's fun
me
Maybe it was funny?
Ah, yes! Because you're really attractive
But
Bebop mistreated me a lot.
Editing is too much
Doesn’t he seem like a reliable older brother?
Have you seen that damn bebop?
I don’t think I even know I’m doing it
Aren’t you busy making money?
Taerin, that...
A thoughtful and complex person
How should I deal with them?
Simply ignorant?
Well, it's just a matter of balancing it out.
What is the genre?
Thriller? Romance? Action?
Complex genre?
Ah, well, I don’t know who the other person is.
- Did you kiss?
- uh?
Oh, what!
No...
Ah! What was it like then?
What was it like after that?
I kept thinking about it
Ha...
Then the senior does it.
Let’s turn it around, just think about your senior.
Oh, oh!
Well, what is that?
What should I do? uh?
So, if you just say you do it, what happens?
Will it work?
cute
Ah, I'm a senior
Just doing this makes me feel bad
I'm jealous
Is there anyone like Nongae?
Sacrifice and devote yourself to me
love only me
someone who dies for a cause
Hey, where are you going for the interview?
My ideal type is Nongae
Just talk, okay?
Just do it inside
Well, anyway, go back.
- Now, for example
- Yes
sit like this
Shall we try eating tteokbokki?
- Is the tteokbokki too spicy?
- Yes, it's spicy.
That...
Why not ice cream?
Oh, that was a stupid question.
Okay, so
The two of them were eating like this
- Then?
- then?
- Yes
Then
Just hold on
rush
No?
Really...
- Without mood
- Really?
I have to set the mood first.
Ugh
Think of me as that person
Even my seniors always act as my counterpart.
Yes!
Now
Close your eyes
I'm immersed
Uh...
What are you doing?
Are you just going to watch?
ah!
I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it
Why?
I'm shaking
Wow, really
Try it like this
Huh?
moody
rush
Because I think of you as my brother
Can't you do it?
to?
this!
Ouch! This...
You, you!
You are Sunwoohae, you are Sunwoohae
How did you know?
Oh, I wanted to pretend not to know
The only men around my senior are
Do it with your brother
Kim, Seokju Kim...
Wait a minute, why are you coming over?
Well, what is it, I’m not interested, I’m not buying it!
Who are you thinking about now?
Weren’t you trying to practice for me?
- Ah, why is my senior showing up?
- senior?
Oh, I've been doing this too lately
Was there no dopamine? No, was there a lot?
You said you were a child before
What kind of bastard are you again?
Are you not focusing on me?
Why am I focusing on you?
That's what you do!
Where are you immersed?
How far have you gone?
uh!
Oh, I have to shake it off.
Oh, let's have a drink.
Okay then, wait a minute.
organizing
By creating a new phase
You mean to make me lose my mind?
That's right
either kiss
Slap your cheek or cry
I have to do something
Or do all of this
Then that brother
Should I just go home and think about that?
I guess so, I guess
Then take a look
I cried and slapped my face
If you kiss, right?
Well, then
You can slap me first and cry
Ah, here it is
- Uh, thank you.
- Hello
- You requested flower pot delivery, right?
- Yes
Payment has been completed
Huh?
Sunwoohae, right?
Ah, yes
It's so amazing
hello, thank you
- have a nice day
- Yes
thank you
Flower delivery has arrived
I saw it on broadcast
Oh, do you deliver it yourself?
Ah, yes
I sign here...
Brother!
Oh, my husband
I'm a real fan
That sitcom, that was really fun.
Just one photo
Let's take a picture together, okay?
- Yes, starting from the signature here...
- Just wait a moment.
Brother!
Oh, why isn't it coming?
stairs
It's too much
It's on the 4th floor, so what if it's so difficult?
-Aren’t you exercising these days?
- Yes
By the way
How was the broadcast?
Was I wise and wise?
Oh, so so so much
It was quirky and lovely.
You've been to the bookstore, really?
- That can't be possible.
- As expected
Stay
I'll give you the script for parts 3 and 4.
Has the chair arrived yet?
They sent it to my parents’ house.
Ah
This box is very sturdy
Ha...
The person who sent the office chair to my home
Script reviewed?
Can't you see Mr. Joy?
I sent you to the academy to get your driver’s license.
Oh my
Are you here?
Excuse me
What is it? Oh my
To see Director Bang Hanna...
Ah...
I didn't know there was anyone else
I only bought two drinks.
I'll drink it well
Our actor
I need to find a new tax accountant.
If you are busy, someone else
You can also recommend it.
You know the person sitting over there, Mr. Mo Tae-rin, right?
He is our representative actor.
That's it.
Are you looking after your mother's work?
If you're uncomfortable...
It's okay
Thank you very much
My name is Seokju Kim.
Please take care of me
Did you commit tax fraud?
Yes, day job
my bag
When can I get it back?
Didn't you just abandon me?
Exchange it with a handkerchief.
What I lent you back then
just have it
You don’t say ‘hey’ today
I guess they decided to be respectful again?
where am i
You were going to take me with you then?
at the hotel
I got curious
I don't care what people think
I know a place where I can cry
in that hotel
Why do you know that place?
I guess I cried a lot there too, well.
It was kind of a favor.
It's treated like a modified work.
Boom?
Even if you stab me, not a single drop of blood
I don't think you'll come out.
If you stab it, it will come out, I’m human too.
You feel unfair to me
I think you have some
Gradually release it
Should I get it now?
I was a little nervous because it was my first radio show.
Well, it reminded me of when I was young.
A broadcast that a senior used to do
I heard it on the rooftop
I once cried at that voice
Just sometimes
Do you ever feel like that?
I feel like gravity is pressing especially on me
I just get to explore it periodically.
Why am I in the middle of this
Am I standing there?
I guess I'm still just a teenager
Why do you keep crying?
So you're going into the water?
Well...
Ah
Tax evasion is a no-no.
I'd like to ask you to save some tax too.
To state the obvious...
It's really funny
What's funny if you don't laugh?
What, human or robot?
Really...
Don't forget my bag next time
Anyway, it's strange
Do you know Nuri’s grades?
Ah, yes
It's hard in Seoul
Able to support with practical skills
This is what school is like
Because I have an aptitude for photography.
I also work hard in my department activities.
- A photo?
- Yes
If you quit one academy,
I think it would be good
There's nothing we can do if it's too hard for you.
No, I will.
I'm sorry, but
The exact relationship with Nuri is
How are you?
Ah, Nuri
I said my brother was coming
As far as I know, the last names are different.
It's family
Because of family circumstances.
Please pay more attention
I think it would be good
Because it's a sensitive time
Yes, sir, I will.
Hello, brother
This is my friend Choi Sarang.
I'm surprised
hello
Hey, are you crazy?
No, why...
brother
Um...
Friends are
What rank are you in?
1st place in the whole school
Um...
What rank are you in?
me?
Why are you asking if you know?
Happiness is not in order of grades
Why are you asking? It's rude.
Your grades are more rude
What did your homeroom teacher say?
Did you not have a good consultation?
You said you take pictures?
Didn’t you mention that the camera is expensive?
Oh, that's just a side activity.
Because it's just for a moment
So are you angry?
Next time, show me too
four photos
Share this with your friends
Don't give it to him
Going
Did I get filmed by you?
I don't know
Crying, hitting and kissing?
no
Hitting, crying, kissing...
Close?
huh?
Yes, hello
Oh, I guess that’s Seonwoo?
Yes, did you pick up that phone?
Oh, no.
Then, where is it...
Oh, yes, yes, I'll go now, yes
If it's not urgent
Please come again
This house is good at flowers.
yes
I must have grown up smelling flowers.
Seonwoohae
Are you Seonwoo?
Oh, you're the person who spoke on the phone earlier?
Oh yes, hello
I'm still running errands
Because it will come soon
Take a look
yes
Ha... I'm losing momentum.
Ah, why do I keep missing it?
Ah, that
I will also buy a book
Oh my, I was looking too closely.
No, the visitor who came our year
Because it's my first time
- Ah...
- I was wondering who you were again.
- Right?
- yes?
Wow, this far
I saw you coming
The two of you are so sweet...
Hey, uh, old man!
Change the light bulb
Don't play in the dark!
yes, okay
Hey
What is it, ayu
Why...
Hey, hey, aren’t you going quickly?
How did you find out about this place?
The class president knows everything.
Be careful and live, so
Chi
Are you a regular here?
You seemed friendly earlier.
Don't you remember?
The nurse's room in my high school
teacher
oh my god
I don't remember
Then retire
Is this the goddess of a used bookstore?
Ah, originally
There was a teacher and grandmother.
Teacher since 5 years ago
You are continuing directly.
- I see.
- Yes
If you don't read anything
I feel like my head is empty
I also help here on my days off.
Ugh
Oh, I said don't leave it here.
Old man really...
Hey, I got this as a gift
I guess they sold it
‘It will soon be 100 days for us too’
‘The CSAT ends in 99 days’
I didn't really study these...
Oh, I see.
‘Let’s go to the same university, I love you’
But seeing as they sold this book
I guess we didn't go to the same college.
cute, cute
Is it cute?
Yeah
I'll reach it
That's right
What are you doing?
- Oh my, oh my.
- Hey
- No, put it here...
- I turned off my phone again.
Oh, leave it and...
this book
I want to buy this book
No, he
After stopping by the flower shop for a while,
I finally bought it
I see it again, the person
How did you see it?
There is
There wasn't much to say during the first meeting, so this time
I thought it would go smoothly, but alas.
Ah...
Nam Joon-ho’s wife is so polarizing.
Female managers on this floor
Why are there so many?
Oh, just us
You're not targeting Nam Junho.
Let's decide quickly
In times like this, the position of representative is really not good.
In the end, you have to make a decision that will make you money.
Hey, Taeyeon Jang, let’s go together!
Hey, come quickly!
Do you want to ride a bike?
huh?
no
I can't ride a bike
Ah
you
I feel like there's something on my face
Where? here?
No, no
Just bow down a little.
Is there something on your face?
What are you going to do?
kiss
- What are you doing?
- That's because I have a plan.
do
Kid...
Is that where you meant to break through?
I don't know, I have to try to find out.
Ha, really
No, why are you smiling?
Oh, you keep making me laugh
- Am I funny?
- Uh
Am I just being funny?
Chi
Seong Je-yeon
Huh?
Uh...
bicycle
Shall I tell you?
Sheesh
I
I want to enjoy the feelings that came to me
It feels like such a long time, something like this
Well, my patience
I don't know how long it will last
There is one way to prolong it
play with me
It's vacation
Do it even if you don’t like it
I don't like it
Hey, hey, hey, hey, this is the rooftop!
Hey, hurry up and get here now...
- Wow...
- Ah, ah, ugh!
hey! hey! hey!
Hey, it's still falling.
Sorry, I just wanted to give it a try.
Is it really falling?
riding a horse
Hey, people like this
I wondered why I took a picture, but it was worth taking a picture of.
Look
Hey, look at this facial expression.
Self is
- Hey, do you want to film again?
- Then
- Wait a minute.
- Uh
Yes, hello
Ah! Ah...
Oh, yes, hello, that...
Could it be that I
Take it next time or not
Can you leave it at the door?
Ah, ah, really?
Yes, yes, I will go, yes
Oh...
You try this
I have to go now
- Now?
- No, that...
I decided to have my credit card delivered.
It's coming today
Ah, leave it behind.
I have to sign it.
- Ah...
- I'm sorry.
Then I
- I'll go.
- Yes, go in.
Well played
me too
Go in
- I'm going
- Uh
- Go in carefully.
- Yes
It's really strange
uh
Uh, I'm in.
What, why does it get brighter when I come in?
Is there a sensor?
Are the flowers okay?
I think it'll be okay for about half a day.
I even finished adding water.
It’s amazing that this has a refrigeration function.
There's no refrigerator
I bought it because I like what I have.
Why did you come?
Ah
This
To give you a photo
Huh?
I have two of the same thing
Wow...
Today is a really strange day.
I also found out what my younger brother was hiding.
The store suddenly has a power outage.
Doesn’t someone suddenly appear at the used bookstore?
It’s been a while since I rode a bike
The rain came suddenly too
But
you
Are there more?
I don't even know what's ahead
I've been with you since long ago
My situation, this kind of thing
I feel like I can't remember much and that's it.
Uh, hey, hey, hey, hey, you...
What's wrong?
Just stay still
The atmosphere
I think it's done
No, it works...
What happens?
me now
We were talking about something serious.
Did you hear?
therefore
me today
I just thought about this
Kid! Hey, Seong Je-yeon, you...
You, you think too much
Huh? think less
opportunity to avoid
There was
There wasn't
Seong Je-yeon
you are really strong
on the weekend
Can you tell me about the bike?
- Hello
A place for the kids to rest
When you whine to make it
I wondered why I needed it
Good
At that time, I carried my gun
The one who hit me was Bang Hanna.
Without fear
How is work these days?
I am reflecting sufficiently
I will work hard at everything
Taerin leaves
There is no actor in charge
Does it feel like you’re floating?
Good news, bad news
There are two things
Good news is
We decided to recruit Nam Jun-ho.
It's so good
You've been waiting for it for quite some time
Bad news is
You should quit, manager.
Me? Me?
why?
Nam Jun-ho’s wife picked you up.
I don't know why
That's it
Do you think this makes sense?
I don't think so
But I
It's heavier when you put it on the scale
I'm the one you have to choose
The company needs Nam Jun-ho
Let's go to another department
If you're not the manager, there's no problem.
I am not the manager
Why is there no problem?
That's the biggest problem for me
I'm really on this floor
At one end
Six years, I worked for six years.
Others change jobs three or four times.
During the time when I was paid ransom and promoted
I sacrificed myself here
Because the CEO is there
That bastard’s back is my bastard
It doesn't feel refreshing to get rid of it
There are a lot of things I am thankful for so far.
I don't know today
I'll take a vacation
Ah...
It really sucks, really.
I
Hitting the calculator
I was just waiting for severance pay.
Now...
Now it's a leap
Company car...
What about the house?
I look like I'm sitting down
What should I do with the monthly rent?
It's mine
There isn't one
They say it might rain tomorrow
Maybe I can't ride a bike?
If it rains, let’s play something else.
Yeah, what are you doing?
Uh, I'm working, why?
Because I miss you
Ah
no
We'll see you tomorrow
What's going on?
no, there isn't
just
I guess I wanted to hear your voice
Should I go?
no
It's okay because I heard your voice
- I guess you're a guest.
- Welcome, just a moment.
I'll hang up
I'm so happy
How are you, Noori?
In Seon Woo-chan’s words,
They say they are raising it.
Is it real?
Did you tell me to go here?
I watched the broadcast
When living together
He brags about his son so much
I remembered it as soon as I saw it
whenever needed
He asked me to take away the documents.
If you ask me where my child is, I keep my mouth shut.
If it weren't for that broadcast, I wouldn't have found it.
I secretly left it away again
I thought you were just doing a show for me
What I threw away
I think it's the same for both of us
At least for now
I ended up assuming the role of a human being.
I didn't have much time to spare at that time.
Prosperously
The one who sets up a store and lives there
I don't know how you feel
paternal love, maternal love
It springs up as soon as it becomes fat.
a young person
I guess you went through a lot of trouble.
I'm definitely not asking for my child back.
It's just shameless, but I want to see it
Sometimes while watching
I want to get to know you slowly
That's enough
Please
sorry
thank you
For coming without being too late
I will also forward this to Nuri.
thank you
Oh...
Kiss listens well to medicine, doesn’t it?
Uh, why?
take a look outside
The moon has risen, look at the moon
The moon that rises every day, that's special
um
Ah, that's kind of nice.
Good, huh?
Yeah
Hey there
Stop looking at the moon
Would you like to look down a little?
huh?
what?
Why are you here?
I said I wanted to see you. Would you like to come down?
no
I just want to see you here
I can see it clearly from here too, your face is big
Should I just do your face?
What are you here for? To filter out a fight?
Are we going to keep talking like this?
Do you know what I'm going to say?
me today
It was very difficult
Why?
who?
uh? What is it? tell me
Just a company
But when I saw your face
Run out right away
I want to do Ganggangsoowollae.
That doesn't work
I guess I'm getting older
I was nineteen, right?
I ran out right away
You must have had a hard time today
Okay
rest well
Yeah
that day
Mom said you would like it too
Going
sleep well
Kid...
Ah...
Oh, I took a vacation.
Seong Je-yeon
I won't burden you
Seong Je-yeon, you are a sick man.
What do you think?
I'm a little sick...
Oh, really...
Oh my
come quickly
Now the customer
I can't answer the phone
The power is off
Connected to voicemail
Call charges will apply after the beep.
Ha...
Are you out of your mind?
- Brother
- Uh, this is the hospital.
When you answered the phone and went
I was passed out
- Oh, it's ruined.
-Why, why, does it hurt?
Oh, I have to...
You can't close your eyes!
You can't cross the river! You...
It hurts, bro.
Oh, sorry, sorry.
Brother, where is my cell phone...
Uh, hey, hey, hey
No, no, no.
lie down, lie down
Please take out the IV for me.
Hey, hey, this
How can I get rid of it because I’m scared?
And the medicine didn't work, just hold on.
My brother has Seong Je-yeon’s phone number.
Agent, because of that.
Uh, I didn't save it.
I'll take a look, do you have any call records?
Oh, I have to go.
I have to go...
Ha, really
Why are you doing this to me too?
Seong Je-yeon
Hey
Since when are you here...
Huh?
Hey
Why are your hands so cold?
First of all, let's go in
Hey, Jeyeon...
Hey, wait a minute
Wait, wait a minute
me today
Something happened
I was trying to contact you quickly
I left my phone at home
So...
I
I guess I really like you
Looking at your face
I feel relieved
I was so scared
I thought about it all
Where does it hurt?
No, did something happen?
The blood dried for half a day
Oh, and why
Don’t use an umbrella!
i am sorry
This will never happen again
promise, then
promise...
promise
If you can't do it
Huh?
If something like this happens again
Anyway
no matter how you go
The end will be like this
What?
We should stop watching
Why is the story like that?
me too
I think I knew
Even though I know
The only reason you hesitate
There must be a reason for that.
I guess I wanted to believe it
To you I
just
That's about it.
yes
let's stop
Uh, bro
Uh, I have to, where is it?
me today
I don't think I can leave the store, I'm sorry
Hey, what am I sorry about?
Is the store in trouble now?
Hey, let's go to the hospital.
You already fell down
Huh? Isn’t it fleeting?
Oh, I guess so, I guess it's fleeting
Uh, sorry, bro.
Why do you carry something like this?
'Then why are you stealing?'
'Instead of roses
Would you like to try putting it in a vase?'
'Red-red?'
Ah, why does this read like flirting?
Ha, am I crazy, phew...
If I leave right now, will you save me?
no
They won't save me
What I threw away then
Ah...
Ah! I didn't bring that handkerchief.
I told you to branch out
You're not buying a chair?
I guess he sent it home.
Everyone lives like that.
In the name of Mr. Motae-rin
Bankbook transaction details, card details, etc.
I will send you a list of documents by email.
Today’s bankbook transaction details
You can give me even last month’s stuff.
yes
But my public certificate
It's on Jeyeon's laptop.
Leave that to me?
You have a lot of trust in the person in charge.
I just need to get it reissued...
Wait a minute
I called Jeyeon sunbae and
I'll ask you to bring it.
Ah...
Hey, senior, where are you? What are you doing?
You really don't listen
Uh, okay.
I have an important meeting so I have to hang up.
After... last, last
Ha...
Hang up, I'm in an important meeting.
Team leader, I heard you were on vacation.
very long
If the team leader is not there
Then who should I ask?
Well, there is no actor in charge right now.
Ah, while I was at work
I have never used annual leave
Is it that expensive?
I don't know
I want to at least drive
Give it to me
Tell me honestly, are you going to quit?
Hey, it's exactly the same size.
Taking more than 10 days of vacation
Is it because you were pushed out by Dongjun?
Nam Jun-ho is in charge?
Ah...
That's how it ended up
At a specific stationery store
Account transfers occur frequently
What did you buy?
Are you digging here too?
Well done learning
What did you buy at a specific stationery store?
- Shovel?
- Oh, that...
soap bubbles
When you want to smoke instead...
Nice to meet you
I make soap bubbles too.
What do you do?
- Bubble gun? Bubble machine?
- Oh no, no way
- You have to blow it yourself.
- oh!
That's right
Just press the button and it comes out
What's the fun?
There is no romance
Our opinions are exactly the same.
I worked hard on this too
It's good to blow
I can't handle the expenses.
What about vehicles?
Lease, your own car, which one do you use?
When do you have time again?
I wish it would blow for a day
Didn’t you hate me?
What if I don’t like it?
There are soap bubbles that I can't do alone.
Let’s do it together, selflessly.
Oh, it's really strange.
Even if it’s strange, let’s do it together
I really wanted to try it
It means that
I saw Mo Tae-rin doing it.
It's strange that I don't drink
Ha...
Welcome
I can't get over my anger
When I lie down to sleep
Your face is floating
Amazing
It's a shame
Have you been drinking?
Yes, I drank it.
All I can do is that
There is no one, why?
In the meantime, I'm afraid that my appearance will be ugly.
Don't do that
I should have given it to you coolly.
I'll just endure it once
I'll endure it one more time
It's annoying to even think about that!
Hey, until today.
Something like you
Until today, I'm shaking wildly
I'll forget everything
forever
forever, forever
I won't pretend to know forever!
yes
What is it?
someone I know
You weren't this kind of person
What did I do so wrong?
you didn't do anything wrong
It's all because of me
Let's go, I'll take you there
Let go
Hey, be careful.
Oh, don't catch it!
- wake up
- Let go
Let go! Let go!
Don't hold it
Don't follow me
Ha...
I told you not to follow me, right?
Am I funny?
that day
I see you crying because of me
You came to vent your anger
Because I might not be there
I'm a little worried about that
you you
Because I didn't want to waste it
funny
Who cares about whom?
Jeyeonah
me
They say it hurts
It feels real now